{"data":[{"question":"The zenith provides a means for making various calculates in astronomy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a means ","b":"for making ","c":"calculates ","d":"astronomy","answer":"3","explain":"- Calculates-> calculations","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"A merger is a combination of two or more businesses down below a single management.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a combination of ","b":"more ","c":"down below ","d":"single ","answer":"3","explain":"- Down below-> under","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Bats rely on their hearings to navigate and to find food at night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"on ","b":"hearings ","c":"to find ","d":"at ","answer":"2","explain":"- Hearings-> hearing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Our urge to classify different life forms and give us names seems to be as old as the human race.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"urge ","b":"us ","c":"seems ","d":"old ","answer":"2","explain":"- Us-> them","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Mount St. Helens, a volcano in Washington State in the United States, erupted in Mary 18, 1980. \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a ","b":"in Washington State ","c":"in the United States","d":"erupted in Mary 18, 1980","answer":"4","explain":"- Erupted in Mary 18, 1980-> Erupted on May 18, 1980","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Despite of its isolation in the Sunda Strait  between Java and Sumatra, over 36,000  people died in the tidal waves following the explosion of Krakato.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Despite of ","b":"in the Sunda Strait  ","c":"between Java ","d":"in the tidal waves ","answer":"1","explain":"- Despite of-> despite","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Many of the satellites of space carry telescopes and other instruments used in astronomy to look at the stars.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Many of the satellites ","b":"of space ","c":"used in astronomy ","d":"look at the stars","answer":"2","explain":"- Of space-> in space","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Wood, the hardened material from which trees are composed, is made up of millions of tiny  tubes of fibers packed together.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"material from which ","b":"composed","c":"made up of millions","d":"of tiny tubes of fibers ","answer":"2","explain":"- Composed-> composed of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Animals that live in areas that are covered in show in winter change the color of their coat according the seasons.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"live in areas ","b":"covered in","c":"in winter ","d":"according ","answer":"4","explain":"- According-> according to ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The dodo, a giant bird now extinct, lived on the island of Mauritius, in Indian Ocean.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The dodo","b":"extinct","c":"lived on ","d":"in Indian Ocean","answer":"4","explain":"- In Indian Ocean-> Indian Ocean","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}